-各位好啊  -好
- Hey, gentlemen. - Hello.
如果你们有人还在想情人节要做什么
If any of you are looking for something to do on Valentine's Day,
我跟艾米将首次在网上直播
Amy and I'll be streaming our first-ever
我们的《有趣的旗帜》节目
live episode of Fun With Flags.
欢迎你们加入我们  一起来庆祝
You're welcome to join us as we celebrate the timeless
风与飘扬布料那永恒的爱恋
love affair between wind and flapping fabric.
我跟佩妮那天晚上定好餐厅吃饭了
Penny and I have dinner reservations that night,
其他任何时间  我们也不看
but any other time, no.
抱歉  我跟妮妮要给新浴缸来个"启用仪式"
Sorry, Bernie and I are breaking in the new hot tub,
懂我说的是啥意思吧
if you know what I mean.
完全不懂  拉杰呢
Not a clue. Raj?
跟艾米丽共度情人节
Spending Valentine's Day with Emily.
你听起来不是太期待啊
You don't sound very excited about it.
没有啊  我挺期待吧
Oh, I am, I am. I g... I guess
可能我还不确定我跟艾米丽到底适不适合
I'm still wondering if Emily and I are right for each other.
这不会跟喝咖啡的那个女生有关吧
Does this have to do with that girl you had coffee with?
你是说那位我魂萦梦牵的身心灵完美女神吗
You mean the strong, sexy angel I can't stop thinking about?
谁知道啊
Who can say?
你念叨着要跟艾米丽分手多久了
You've been talking about breaking up with Emily forever.
你为什么不赶紧分了得了
Why don't you just do it already?
早死早超生
Yeah, just get it over with.
你们说得好像很简单
Well, you say it like it's easy.
你们之中有任何人跟别人分手过吗
Have any one of youever broken up with anyone?
-没  -不太
- No. - Not really.
有一次我不小心叫了车
You know, uh, once I ordered an Uber by accident.
我只能默默上车  随便去了个地方
I just got in and went somewhere.
你真的要跟她分手吗
So, you really gonna break up with her?
我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
有任何建议吗
Do you have any advice?
我这一生甩过无数男子
Well, I have broken up with my fair share of guys.
你知道我甩过莱纳德几次吗
I mean, how many times did I break up with Leonard?
第四次之后我就不数了
I stopped counting at four.
我给你的建议就是去她家提分手
All right, my advice to you is do it at her place
这样你需要走人时就随时能走
so you can leave when you need to,
实话实说  快刀斩乱麻
uh, tell the truth, make it quick
做好会有人喷泪的准备
and be prepared for tears.
我已经打算在进她家前先预哭一场
Oh, I'm gonna do a pre-cry before I go in there.
先把我的眼泪哭干
Really dry myself out.
她指的是艾米丽
She meant Emily.
没  真的不是指她
No, I-I really didn't.
你真的要跟我分手吗
You're seriously breaking up with me?
是的
Yeah.
然后你觉得在情人节前提分手
And you thought right before Valentine's Day
是好时机吗
was a good time to do it?
有道理  那我们几天后再谈吧
You're right-- let's talk again in a few days.
克莱儿  是我  拉杰什
Hey, Claire. Hi. It's-it's Rajesh.
不知道你情人节那天有没有空
I was-I was wondering if you're free for Valentine's Day?
抱歉  我刚跟我男朋友复合
Sorry, I just got back with my boyfriend.
但我为了你甩了我女朋友呢
But I just broke up with my girlfriend.
情人节前甩人家吗
Right before Valentine's Day?
真是个渣男
What an ass.
求你别不要我  我们的爱是天作之合
Please take me back. Our love was meant to be!
我情人节要当单身狗了
I'm gonna all alone on Valentine's Day.
你说得真没错  喷泪
Well, you were right-- tears.
22分钟后我们就要开始直播了
Okay, and we are live in 22 minutes.
我好紧张  希望观众们能来收看
I'm nervous. I hope people will be around to watch
哪怕今天是情人节
even though it's Valentine's Day.
收看旗帜知识网络节目的观众们吗
People who are fans of an Internet show about flags?
放心吧  情人节他们绝对有空
Trust me, they're around.
说到情人节  我今晚
Oh, and speaking of Valentine's Day, I haven't
才不会忘记你呢
forgotten about you tonight.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你现在变成了我生命中与这节目
Well, you've become such an integral part of my life
不可分割的一部分
as well as this show,
我觉得应该把你加入到节目名字中
I felt it only right to include your name in the title.
你真是太贴心了
That is so sweet.
从今天开始  这个节目的名称将会是
So from now on, this program will be officially known as
谢尔顿·库珀博士
Dr. Sheldon Cooper
与艾米·菲拉·福勒博士
and Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler
倾情奉献  谢尔顿·库珀博士的《有趣的旗帜》
present Dr. Sheldon' Cooper's Fun With Flags.
朗朗上口啊
Catchy.
我去检查一下浴缸的温度
I'm gonna check the temp on the tub.
别弄太热
Don't make it too hot.
抱歉  但"太热"辣
Sorry, but "too hot"
是本美男唯一的温度
is the only temperature I come in.
看看
Look at that--
光溜溜的青龙
you shaved it all.
不用谢
You're welcome.
提问  这是我首次泡按摩浴缸
Um, question-- this is my first hot tub--
里面有耗子漂浮着是正常的吗
is it supposed to come with a rat flopping around in it?
真的吗  快弄走
Ew, really? Get it out.
怎么弄
How?
我们有个漏勺就好了
Uh... wish we had a skimmer.
你把按摩喷头关掉
Uh, you turn off the jets,
我去厨房拿滤网
I'll get a strainer from the kitchen.
我不知道怎么关掉喷头
I don't know how to turn off the jets.
很好  我也不知道你滤网收哪
Good, I don't know where we keep the strainer.
借过
Excuse me.
有坏消息
Uh, bad news.
领班说至少还得等一小时
The maitre d' said it's gonna be at least an hour.
一小时  别闹了  我们明明订了位
An hour? What? That's crazy. We have a reservation.
-对啊  -那你怎么说的
- I know. - So what did you say?
谢谢  抱歉打扰了
Thanks, sorry to bother you.
我用恶狠狠的语气说的
But I said it like a badass.
你就不能比如...
All right, well, can't you, like,
塞点钱贿赂他之类的吗
slip him some money or something?
真的吗  我没这么做过  真能行吗
Really? I've never done that before. Does it work?
你是在问我"人们喜不喜欢钱"吗
Do people like money-- is that what you're asking?
某个知识量小到以为
A... A lot of attitude from the woman
mc2是饶舌歌手名的人  脾气倒是挺大啊
who thought MC squared was a rapper.
大过节的你这么说明智吗
Now, is that a smart thing to say on a holiday
今晚基本算是全国操操夜
that's basically national sex night?
对不起  你很漂亮  我是白痴
I'm sorry. You're pretty, I'm stupid.
你好
Hello.
麻烦再看看到霍夫斯塔德了没
Just checked again for Hofstadter.
还要等一小时吗
Still gonna be an hour?
恐怕是的
I'm afraid so.
好的  谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
这可能是你掉的吧
I think you may have dropped this?
谁丢了一张20块
Did anybody lose a 20?
我
I did.
我都处理好了
Oh, I took care of it.
马上开始直播
Okay, we are live
5  4  3
in five, four, three...
等等  糟糕  我已经按下按钮了
Oh, wait. Oh, shoot, I already pushed the button.
没关系  直播已开始
Never mind, we're live.
大家好
Uh, hello
欢迎收看直播特别版
and welcome to a special live edition
谢尔顿·库珀博士
of Dr. Sheldon Cooper...
与艾米·菲拉·福勒博士出品的
and Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler present...
谢尔顿博士的《有趣的旗帜》
Dr. Sheldon Cooper's Fun With Flags.
请将今晚这一集
Consider tonight's episode
当作送给你们的情人节礼物吧  观众们
a Valentine's Day gift for you, our viewers.
同时也是我送你的礼物
It's also my gift to you.
这够明显了  对吧
That was clear, right?
因为你不会得到别的礼物了
'Cause you're not getting anything else.
鉴于我们是在直播
Since we're live,
你们终于可以即时联系到我们
you'll finally be able to reach out to us
提出你们的旗思旗问
with your flag thoughts and flag questions.
我们先快速回答几个常有人问的问题
Allow us to answer a few quick ones that we get all the time.
是的  我真的是一名博士
Uh, uh, yes, I really am a doctor.
是的  她真的是我的女朋友
Uh, yes, she really is my girlfriend.
不是  我只是习惯老眨眼
No, I just blink a lot,
并不是在打摩斯密码求救
it's not Morse code for "Rescue me."
好的
Oh, uh, ok...
有观众打进第一通电话
Uh, here's our first call.
你好  欢迎来到《有趣的旗帜》
Hello, and welcome to Fun With Flags.
你有什么问题吗
What's your question?
我脑子是哪里有病
What is wrong with me?
为什么我总是自我毁灭
Why am I so self-destructive?
拉杰什
Rajesh?
是我
Yes.
每当事情一帆风顺时  我总有方法毁掉它
Whenever things are going well, I always find a way to ruin it.
你俩看起来很幸福  是怎么做到的
You two look happy-- how do you do it?
我觉得是始于良好的沟通
I-I think it starts with good communication.
是啊  等等  这问题跟旗帜无关
Yeah, wait, that's not a flag question.
下一位
Next caller.
我希望你不会认为我这么说
I hope you don't think I'm just saying this
是因为今天是情人节  但...
because it's Valentine's Day, but...
我真的好爱你
I love you so much.
我要把这玩意扔进你浴袍里
I'm gonna put this down your robe.
它不动了  但我觉得它还活着
It's not moving, but I think it's still alive.
那该把它扔回去多泡几分钟吗
Well, should we put it back in there a few minutes?
不必
No.
这不是老鼠  是只兔子
No, and it's not a rat, it's a rabbit.
我们得救救它
We need to save it.
我们该怎么做
Well, how do we do that?
我不知道  你用手机查查
Um, I don't know, look it up on your phone.
我拿毛巾包着它
I-I'm gonna wrap it in a towel.
"照顾受伤的兔子"
"Taking care of injured rabbit."
有了
Okay.
确保它既舒服又暖和
Make sure it's comfortable and warm.
它刚泡在热水浴缸里  这条符合
Well, it was just in a hot tub. I'm gonna say "Check."
还有别的吗
Anything else?
确保它没有脱水
To make sure it's not dehydrated,
喂他一勺电解质溶液
feed him an electrolyte solution.
如果没有反应
If it's not responding,
用一块暖布帮他擦洗脸和生殖器
use a warm cloth to wash its face and genitals.
好耶
Yeah.
这真是太过分了
This is ridiculous.
我要去找那个领班谈谈
You know, I'm gonna go talk to the maitre d.
你要说什么
What are you gonna say?
我不知道  我去嗲他几下吧
I don't know. I'm... I'm gonna flirt with him.
我不知道我是否能接受这事
I don't know if I'm comfortable with that.
我今晚还是跟你"睡"啊
I'm still sleeping with you tonight.
你看看能不能弄到靠窗的桌子
See if you can get a table by the window.
你好  你叫什么
Hi there. What's your name?
-格伦  -天啊
- Glen. - Oh, boy,
今晚这里人真是超多啊  格伦
it is crazy in here tonight, huh, Glen?
-情人节嘛  你懂的  -是啊
- Well, you know, Valentine's Day. - Yes.
我猜你女友一定超级郁闷
Bet your girlfriend is super bummed
你今晚得上班
you had to work tonight.
听着  我们等了挺长时间了  我有点...
Anyway, look, we have been waiting a while, and I just...
恕我直言  女士
With all due respect, ma'am,
我无能为力
there's nothing I can do.
你用不着叫我"女士"
You don't have to call me ma'am.
好的
Okay.
我们应该年纪相仿
I mean, we're basically the same age.
好的
Okay.
你几岁
How old are you?
我21岁  你呢
I'm 21. How old are you?
把嘴闭上  格伦
Just shut up, Glen.
走吧  我们离开这里
Come on, let's get out of here.
-为什么  -因为姐年轻  走吧
- What? Why? - Because I'm young. Let's go.
拉杰什  分手后
Rajesh, it's perfectly normal
产生自我怀疑非常正常
to have doubts after breaking up with someone.
你真的这么认为吗
Well, you really think so?
是啊  你知道什么不正常吗
Yeah, you know what's not normal?
在一个旗帜节目里哭诉个人情绪
Blubbering about emotions during a flag show.
除非那种情绪是因为新西兰要变更国旗
Unless that emotion is excitement over New Zealand
喜极而泣
changing their flag.
祝你们好运哦  疯狂的新西兰人
Yeah, good luck, you crazy Kiwis,
我们全力支持你们
we're rooting for you.
你的朋友正在伤心呢
Your friend is hurting.
不  谢尔顿说得对
No, Sheldon's right.
艾丽米说过我老对自己的感受喋喋不休
Emily did say I always talk about my feelings too much.
我想
I-I suppose that
这应该算是恋爱中需要注意的一点
could be a legitimate concern in a relationship.
甚至可以算作恋爱路上的危险红旗
Uh, perhaps even a-a red flag.
说到红旗
And speaking of red flags,
请看这面来自前苏联的性感红旗
check out this sexy number from the former Soviet Union.
相当地诱人吧
Hubba, hubba.
又有一位观众打电话来了
Uh, we-we have another caller.
你好  这里是《有趣的旗帜》
Hi. You're on Fun with Flags.
你好  我也想倾诉下我有多孤独
Hello. I want to talk about how lonely I am, too.
克里普克  是你吗
Kripke? Is that you?
是我  我独自一人坐在电脑前
Yeah, I'm just sitting here all by myself
思考着我这辈子是否还能找到我的爱人
wondering if I'll ever find someone to share my life with.
最好是亚洲人  18至24岁  不能是胖妞
Preferably Asian, 18-24, no fatties.
拜托  所有的留言和问题
Please, all comments and questions
都必须和旗帜有关
should be flag-related.
好啊  我裤裆中的"旗杆"算吗
All right. Is my pole flag-related?
当然算啦
I don't see why not.
他开始吃东西了  这是个好现象
He's eating. That's a good sign.
吃饭以后要等上一个小时
You're gonna have to wait one hour
才能再游泳哦
until you can go swimming again.
-他好可爱哦  -的确
- He's pretty cute. - He is.
我们应该...给他取名吗
Should we... name him?
今天是情人节[圣华伦丁节]
It is Valentine's Day.
就叫华伦天奴怎么样
How about Valentino?
很好  很经典的小兔名字
Nice. A classic rabbit name.
彼得兔  罗杰兔
Peter Rabbit, Roger Rabbit.
华伦天奴·沃罗威茨兔
Valentino Wolowitz Rabbit.
看看你茂密的胸毛和小龅牙
Oh, look at all that chest hair and overbite.
完全就是沃罗威茨家族的一员呀
Of course you're a Wolowitz.
我勒个去  他咬了我
Son of a bitch! He bit me!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
当然有事了
No, I'm not okay!
野兔可能携带狂犬病呢
Wild rabbits can have rabies!
谁叫你把手指放在他的嘴边
Oh. Well, why did you put your finger near its mouth?
明显是因为我犯傻嘛
Poor judgment, obviously.
他这么小   我想应该没事的
He's so little. I'm sure it's fine.
怎么可能没事  我刚刚被一只
How can it be fine? I just got attacked
具有反犹太倾向的野生动物袭击了
by a clearly anti-Semitic wild animal.
虽然和我们原计划不一样
It's not what we planned,
但这样也不坏  对吧
but this isn't so bad, right?
这实在是太赞了
It is freaking amazing.
很高兴看你心情好一点了
Well, glad you're feeling better.
我刚才是又饿又憋气
I was just hungry and cranky,
我从来没被人叫过"女士"呢
and I've never been called "Ma'am" before.
-这件事很严重吗  -算严重吧
- Is that a big deal? - Kind of.
你第一次被叫作"先生"是什么时候
When was the first time someone called you "Sir"?
小学六年级
Sixth grade,
当时我穿着休闲西装  提着公文包  所以...
but I wore a sport coat and carried a briefcase, so...
你能相信我遇见你时才22岁吗
Can you believe when I met you I was 22?
真是时光匆匆啊
I mean, it's crazy!
时间都去哪儿了
Where did all that time go?
都被你用来看《单身汉》相亲节目了
Mm, you watched The Bachelor a lot.
你想开玩笑就开吧
Yeah, go ahead and make jokes,
但你的三十岁也马上就要过完了
but your thirties are almost over.
才怪
No, they're not.
比起30岁来  你更接近40岁了
You're closer to 40 than you are 30.
你嫁给了一个老头子
You married an old man.
这样吧  今晚我们来找点乐子
Tell you what. Let's do something fun tonight.
这又不会让我们变年轻
Won't make us any younger.
也许不会  但等我们真正老去的那天
Well, maybe not, but some day we actually will be old,
我们回想到今晚
and we'll look back on this night
仍然会怀念起今夜的好时光
and remember what a good time we had.
比如什么
Okay, like what?
我想到了  食物大战
I know. Food fight!
我再继续想吧
I'll keep thinking.
我知道你俩为单身而难过
Look, I know you both feel bad about being alone,
但有时最好的解决办法
but sometimes the best thing you can do
就是给自己一点时间
is take a little time for yourself,
尤其是当你刚刚结束一段关系的时候
especially when you just got out of a relationship.
说到结束关系
Speaking of ending relationships,
当英属洪都拉斯改名为伯利兹时
when British Honduras became Belize,
他们设计了一面画着树的国旗
they designed a new flag with a tree on it,
现在我想在那棵树上吊死来结束生命
and I would like to hang myself from that tree.
可是艾米  当你和谢尔顿分手时
But, Amy, when you and Sheldon split up,
你不是立刻就和其他人约会了吗
didn't you start dating someone right away?
我不觉得那算是立刻
Well, I... I wouldn't say right away.
而且  实际上她约会了3个人
And actually, it was three different men.
3个人吗
Three different men?!
我去  妹子  太会主动给猪送白菜了吧
Damn, girl, way to give the milk away?
克里普克好像断线了
Oh, looks like we just lost Kripke.
没有  我还在线上
Actually, I'm still here.
-现在呢  -还在
- Now? - Yup.
- Now? - Yup!
现在呢
Now?
克里普克好像断线了
Oh, looks like we just lost Kripke.
在艾米丽之前  我曾经单身了好长时间
Before Emily, I was alone for so long.
我不知道是否还能再挺过单身的日子
I just... I don't know if I can do that again.
有件事可能会让你开心一点
Well, you know, here is something that might cheer you up.
英属曼岛的国旗
The flag of the Isle of Man
上面是共穿一条奇怪内裤的
is nothing but three legs
三条大光腿  所以...
sharing a weird pair of underpants, so...
你觉得只有你有大问题吗
you think you got problems.
我有个主意
I have an idea.
也许咱们观众中的某人
Maybe someone in our audience
可能会有兴趣和拉杰什见面
would be interested in meeting Rajesh.
姑娘们  我可以证明他是一个善良
Ladies, I can attest that he is a kind,
帅气  聪明
handsome, intelligent...
富二代  别忘了说我是富二代
Rich parents! Don't forget, rich parents!
被宠坏了的天体物理学家  不仅...
...spoiled astrophysicist who not only...
行动够快的
Well, that was quick.
你好  这里是《有趣的旗帜》
Hi. You're on Fun with Flags.
喂  我刚刚好像断线了
Hey, I think I got cut off.
你好  克里普克
Hello, Kripke.
我有一个旗帜问题
I have a flag question.
你睡过几个男人
How many men did you have sex with?
找找  什么东西年轻有趣
Let's see. What's young and fun?
我们可以去跳舞
Uh, we could go dancing.
你是真准备下舞池跳吗
Are you actually gonna dance?
当然了  对啊
Of course. Yeah.
就别害别人得自戳双目了
No one wants to see that.
去海边裸泳如何
Hey, how about skinny dipping at the beach?
不去  我经不起另一种"鱼水之欢"了
No, I don't need any fish nibbling my business.
有《红磨坊》演出
Oh, there's a screening of Moulin Rouge!
听说观众和演员都一起唱
I heard the crowd sings along and stuff.
好像挺有意思的  几点开始
That sounds fun. When's it start?
午夜
Midnight.
午夜  不是吧
Midnight. Really?
管它呢  我们去吧
You know what? Let's do it.
好的  太棒了
Okay, great!
等等  票卖光了
Oh, wait. Uh, it's sold out.
-谢天谢地  -太棒了
-Oh, thank God.  -Yes!
上面说  兔子传播狂犬病的几率很小
It says, rabies in rabbits is highly unlikely.
-太好了  -一点都不好
- Oh, terrific. - It's not terrific.
小概率的事发生得还少吗
Lots of highly unlikely things happen.
你见过这浴袍下的胴体  居然还嫁给我
You saw what's under this robe, and you still married me.
你要是真的担心  就带它去看兽医
If you're really worried, we'll take him to the vet
-让兽医检测一下  -好的  谢谢
- and have him tested. - Good. Thank you.
好  找到个测试
Oh, okay, there is a test!
你只需要...
All they have to do is...
劈开它的头  检查大脑
cut off his head and check his brain.
劈开它的头
Oh, cut off his head?
那小鼻子就在头上呢
That's where his little nose is.
它没有任何狂犬症状
He's not showing any symptoms.
我还是去自己急诊室确认一下吧
I guess I'll just go to the emergency room to be safe.
华仔  这只是你的臆想病犯了
Howie, this is just your hypochondria.
不是  我坐到静音键上
No, when I sat on the mute button
以为自己聋了  那才叫臆想病
and thought I'd gone deaf, that was my hypochondria.
我们另找个时间告诉他我怀孕了吧
We'll find another time to tell him I'm pregnant.
这是我第一次跟人分手
I mean, this is the first time I've ever broken up with someone.
没有想到  会如此心痛
I just... I didn't realize it was gonna hurt this much.
是这样的
It really can.
行了
All right.
这一点都不有趣
Nothing about this is fun.
没人想聊旗帜
No one wants to talk about flags,
而我已经十分钟插不上话了
and I haven't spoken in over ten minutes,
所以互联网  请欣赏新节目
so, enjoy your new show, Internet.
由艾米·菲拉·福勒博士出品的  《的》
Dr. Amy Farrah Flower Present... With.
抱歉打扰到你们了
I'm sorry for bothering you.
我马上挂
I'll hang up now.
不要  等等  拉杰什
No, hold on, Rajesh.
你这样非常没有同情心
You know, you're not being very sympathetic.
分手的痛楚你最清楚不过了
You know firsthand that breakups are hard.
好吧
Fine.
如果你坚持让我参与的话
If you insist on making me a part of this,
是的  我了解这有多痛苦
yes, I knowledge how painful they can be.
尽管如此  这种痛苦有进化的作用
However, pain has an evolutionary purpose.
这让我们获得外部提供的信息
It provides information from the environment
这种行为对我们有负面影响
that, uh, behavior isn't good for us.
比如我爱上了那个脱衣舞女
Like when I fell in love with that stripper
给她买了一辆丰田普锐斯
and bought her a Prius.
我要把所有键都按一遍
I'm just gonna push all the buttons.
拉杰  我很遗憾  你觉得痛苦
Raj, now, I'm sorry you're suffering.
当初我和艾米分手时  我也很痛苦
When Amy and I were broken up, I also suffered.
说起来也许你不信
And this may sound surprising,
但我很感激有过这段磨难
but I'm grateful for having gone through it.
真的吗
Really?
是的
Yes.
我相信我们现在的感情  前所未有的牢固
I believe our relationship now is stronger than ever.
我也是
So do I.
在我们分手期间
When-when we were apart,
我了解到你对我有多重要
I learned how important you are to me.
也意识到  当两个人相爱
And I realize that when two people are in love,
有时候他们...
sometimes they...
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day!
我们年轻又有趣
We are young and fun!
我认错
I stand corrected.
有趣
Fun.
恭喜直播节目成功
Congratulations on a successful live show.
还有美好的情人节
And a lovely Valentine's Day.
打扫清洁真是不年轻也不有趣
Cleaning up is not young and fun.
怎么不是  彩花大战
It can be. Confetti fight!
你去歇会吧
Maybe you should take a break.
我来就好
I got this.
你知道彩花的单数是彩片吗
Did you know the singular of confetti is "confetto"?
有意思  但哪时会需要用单数表示
Interesting, and when would you use the singular?
问得好
I'm glad you asked.
艾米  你鼻子里有一张彩片
Amy, you have a confetto in your nose.
不不不  另一边
No, no, no, no. Other side.
这就对了
There you go.